Benjamin Hinora

Senior Web & Mobile Developer, Web3 Developer

Email: benjaminhinora@gmail.com Phone: (705) 990-2520

Link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/benjamin-hinora

ABOUT ME

Passionate and skilled Blockchain developer offering 8 years of relevant experience and a proven track record of success in achieving extraordinary results. With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team setting.

- 8+ years of professional decentralized application and Defi protocol development experience
- Experienced in a startup role dealing with decentralized and web applications
- Extensive knowledge of Ethereum, EVM, Hyper Ledger, and various consensus protocols
- Proficient with React, Node/Express,
 Javascript/Typescript, Golang, problem-solving, and research skills
- Maintained a remote work role for 4 years

EXPERIENCE

Nuremberg, Bavaria, Germany Jun 2019 - May 2022

Senior Frontend Developer

Roboyo

- Developed responsive websites and web apps based on UI/UX using React.js
- React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Material UI, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Node/Express
- · Postgres, MySQL, MongoDB
- · Setup Heroku instances and manage pipeline

Redwood City, California, United States Jul 2018 - Apr 2019

Frontend Developer

Dexterity, Inc.

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Website and web app development using React.js
- Integrated Chart libraries & implemented Charts using Chart.js, AmCharts and D3.js
- File uploading to AWS S3 and Google Cloud Storage
- API integration (REST API & GraphQL)

Full Stack Engineer

BJIT Inc

Minato, Tokyo, Japan Jul 2012 - Mar 2018

- Developed static web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery and PHP.
- Designed UI/UX using Photoshop and 3DsMax

EDUCATION

2008 - 2012

Bachelor's of Computer Science

Tokyo Institute of Technology

Specialized in Computer Science. Studied main theories of computer science including software-design, project management and Q/A.

SKILLS

- React/Redux(saga, thunk)/Next.js/ReactNative
- JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3
- React/Redux(saga, thunk)/Next.js
- Angular, NgRx, RxJs, PrimeNG
- · Vue, Vuex, Vuetify, Quasar
- Node.js/Express/Nest.js
- Postgres, MySQL, MongoDB
- Material UI, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS
- · Web3, NFT, Cryptocurrency, Ethers, Rainbowkit

LANGUAGES

English Advanced

Japanese Native